<root>
    <row>
        <id>1</id>
        <name>Rooney Murphy</name>
        <role>Founder and CEO</role>
        <description>
            <p>Rooney is the co-founder of AVCSS Renewals and his job is to make sure the company grows in a sustainable, exciting way.  Engineer by Profession, he is good at inspiring the team to achieve bigger and better things, with a  hands-on approach in terms of running the company and delivering service. Roo enjoys spending time cooking at home, running, and traveling for work or holidays.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/RonneMurphy.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>2</id>
        <name>Nick Byrne</name>
        <role>Managing Director</role>
        <description>
            <p>Nick is in charge of the day-to-day operational running of the business, which includes the business strategy, operations, and client services.  Over the past 10 years, he has transformed the way the company operates on what we deliver for our clients, resulting in becoming one of the leaders in the industry national wide. When Nick is not at work, he is usually busy with his four children or following rugby matches.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/nickByrne.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>3</id>
        <name>Sophie Beresford</name>
        <role>Commercial Director</role>
        <description>
            <p>Sophie is responsible for ensuring that the Commercial and marketing strategies are implemented across the company. Her main areas of expertise are financial and professional services.  As part of the management team, she works closely with Ronney and Nick to ensure the company continues growing and developing its service offering.  Sophie loves the fast pace of the job, but in her spare time, she enjoys dancing and learning new languages.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/SophieBeresford.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>3</id>
        <name>Jack Ryan</name>
        <role>Sales and Operations Manager</role>
        <description>
            <p>Jack is responsible for maintaining the quality and standard of the services provided by coordinating the sales and the operations teams. With more than 15 years of experience in Operations, Sales Management, and Engineering, he took the challenge 5 years ago haven’t looked back since. Jack loves to spend time in the country side in his free time, enjoing a good red wine, Irish Wiskey and Italian Food.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/JackRyan.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>5</id>
        <name>Patsy Doyle</name>
        <role>Solar Advisor</role>
        <description>
            <p>Patsy is a solar industry advisor with 4 years of experience. Carl learned all phases of the Solar Industry, getting leads, getting usage, all paperwork, creating proposals, creating designs using multiple programs like Clean Power Tool, Excel, CAD & Sunrun Tools. She is an environmental engineer who enjoys doing social work during weekends, or going to the beach for a walk.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/PatsyDoyle.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>6</id>
        <name>Helen McEneaney</name>
        <role>Wind Advisor</role>
        <description>
            <p>Helen is our wind energy advisor, the primary contact for customers who are considering wind power. Additionally, she is also in charge of pursuing opportunities by monitoring local business developments and identifying potential clients. Passionate about reading, Helen spend most of her free time reading and cooking at home in the company of her little dog Daisy.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/HelenMcEneaney.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>7</id>
        <name>James Galvin</name>
        <role>Project Manager</role>
        <description>
            <p>James is dedicated to the proliferation of solar energy. With 5 years of experience in the industry working for  Green Energy Inc, one of the biggest solar companies in the UK, he relocated to Ireland 3 years ago and joined AVCSS as a Project Manager providing technical and project management expertise to our team.  James enjoys playing chess, and he started a chess club for the elderly in his community. </p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/JamesGalvin.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>8</id>
        <name>Conor Shea</name>
        <role>Field Service Engineer</role>
        <description>
            <p>As a Field Service Engineer, Conor is a key part to play in the success of all our projects, his experience and dedication bring peace of mind to every customer. Conor evaluates all the installations and equipment after maintenance and repairs and runs safety checks. Outside work he enjoys cycling and fishing during the weekends.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/ConorShea.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>9</id>
        <name>Liam Whelan</name>
        <role>Installer | Solar Electrician</role>
        <description>
            <p>Liam is in charge of the Solar Energy Installation Division and served as an installer when required. He has been in the company for over 6 years. Before joining the company, Liam worked in an electrical company, leading the electrical installation team, he is a experimented electritian with more than 20 years of experience. Outside work, Liam loves spend time completing DIY projects with his two sons.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/LiamWhelan.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>10</id>
        <name>Alan Rea</name>
        <role>Installer | Wind Electrician</role>
        <description>
            <p>Alan is in charge of the Wind Energy Installation Division coordinating and supporting the installation team during the projects. He is also the point of contact to our customers for service support, ensuring delivering the best after-sales service. He joined the company  5 years ago as a wind installer while completing his electrician certification. As an active social individual, Alan enjoys going to the gym and playing football to stay fit.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/AlanRea.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>11</id>
        <name>Charlie Meagher</name>
        <role>Solar Installer</role>
        <description>
            <p>Charlie is one of our experimented Solar Installers. He has been working at AVSCC since 2019, he is a flexible and hardworking professional who ensures the best quality of service that our customers expect. In his spare time, Charlie enjoys hanging out with his friends and family watching sports and visiting the local pub.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/CharlieMeagher.jpeg</image>
    </row>
    <row>
        <id>12</id>
        <name>Noah Keenahan</name>
        <role>Wind Installer</role>
        <description>
            <p>Noa is part of our wind division, and a proactive individual who is always giving solutions when they are needed. He also provides maintenance of the turbines performing a series of checks to determine the health of the turbine, replacing any parts when necessary. Noa's hobbies are going to recitals and concerts, playing guitar and meeting new people.</p>
        </description>
        <image>../assets/images/NoahKeenahan.jpeg</image>
    </row>
</root>